humanproofdesigns.com 2017-09-08

# Privacy Policy - Human Proof Designs

Your privacy is important to Human Proof Designs.  This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that Human Proof Designs collects, and the ways in which Human Proof Designs uses that personal information.

**Credit**

This document was created using a Contractology template available at [http://www.freenetlaw.com](http://www.freenetlaw.com/).

**Personal information collection**

Human Proof Designs may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

l  information about your use of this website

l  information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website

l  information about transactions carried out over this website (including email address, paypal account (where different) and name)

l  information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services (including email address and name); and

l  any other information that you send to Human Proof Designs.

**Using personal information**

Human Proof Designs may use your personal information to:

l  administer this website;

l  personalize the website for you;

l  enable your access to and use of the website services;

l  send to you products that you purchase;

l  supply to you services that you purchase;

l  send to you statements and invoices;

l  collect payments from you; and

l  send you marketing communications.

Where Human Proof Designs discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Human Proof Designs may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

**Securing your data**

Human Proof Designs will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

Human Proof Designs will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.

Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be  protected by encryption technology.

**Cross-border data transfers**

Information that Human Proof Designs collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which Human Proof Designs operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

**Updating this statement**

Human Proof Designs may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

**Other websites**

This website contains links to other websites.

Human Proof Designs is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

**Contact Human Proof Designs**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or Human Proof Design’s treatment of your privacy, please contact Human Proof Designs:

by email to dom@humanproofdesigns.com
